firstcallonline.com 2017-06-06

# O'Reilly First Call Auto Parts for the Professional

  * Personal Information
  * Customer Rights
  * Security
  * E-mail

### Personal and Site Usage Information

#### What is collected

O'Reilly Automotive Stores, Inc., may collect information from you and your use of the First Call Online Web site (the "Site"), including, but not limited to: your name, contact and billing information, activity on the Site, and transaction information. On some web pages of the Site, you can order products or services, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are name, contact and billing information, and transaction information. In order to tailor our Web site to continuously improve our products and services, we may also ask you to voluntarily provide us with information regarding your personal or professional interests, demographics, experience with our products, and contact preferences. However, to reiterate, providing such information is completely at your discretion. **O'REILLY RESERVES THE RIGHT TO MODIFY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME AT ITS SOLE DISCRETION, WITH OR WITHOUT NOTICE.**

#### How is it used

O'Reilly uses your information to better understand your needs and provide you with better service and user experience. Specifically, we use your information to help you complete a transaction, to communicate back to you, to update you on service and benefits, to improve the Site and product selection, to troubleshoot reported problems and to personalize our Web site for you. Data collected online may also be combined with information you provide when you register your ownership of O'Reilly products. 

#### Who we share it with

O'Reilly will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to any others. Unless we have your direct permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with other O'Reilly entities and/or business partners who are acting on our behalf for the uses described above. Such O'Reilly entities and/or business partners, including those in the United States and/or any other countries, are governed by our privacy policies with respect to the use of this data and are bound by the appropriate confidentiality agreements O'Reilly may share personal customer provided to O'Reilly with third parties who provide services and products to O'Reilly. Examples of ways in which your information may be used include, but are not limited to, the following:

### Customer Rights

O'Reilly will not use or share any of the personal information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without first letting you know and offering you a choice. As previously stated, we will also provide you the opportunity to let us know if you do not wish to receive unsolicited direct marketing materials from us and we will make commercially reasonable efforts to honor such requests. Local country laws and policies are applied where they differ from those in the U.S. 

### Security

O'Reilly is committed to ensuring the security of your information. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### E-mail

It is critical you provide a valid email address for your security. O'Reilly uses your email address to confirm any activities you perform online and to provide you with important account information. By signing up for account access you are automatically entered to receive communications from O'Reilly Auto Parts and First Call via mail, email, phone and various other channels. Company may use these channels to communicate member account status, product recalls, notify member when they are eligible for a reward, communicate program features and benefits, offer special member promotions we believe may be of interest to you and other information company deems applicable.

### Updates to this Privacy Policy

From time to time, O'Reilly may modify this Privacy Policy. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting notice of those changes on this page. O'Reilly recommends that you periodically check back to this page for any updates.

### How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this site, please contact us via e-mail at fcallreg@oreillyauto.com.
